manchesterconfidential.co.uk 2014-10-09

# Privacy | Manchester Confidential

**The Confidentials ; Privacy Statement**

 **The Confidentials** are committed to providing you with excellent and relevant content on both our website and within any emails we may send out to you as part of our marketing efforts. Because we respect your right to privacy, we have developed this Privacy Statement to inform you about our privacy practices for the entire **The Confidentials** umbrella. (Which covers all of our websites).

Please note that we may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and perusal, **The Confidentials** are not responsible for the policies or practices of these other sites.

Questions regarding this privacy policy should be directed to [privacy@theconfidentials.co.uk](mailto:privacy@theconfidentials.co.uk). Please contact that email address with any queries.

 **Overview**  
Privacy is a concern to most users of the internet and is a basic requirement for an enjoyable experience online. At **The Confidentials** we are fundamentally aware of this and are sensitive to the privacy concerns of our subscribers and any other visitors to our website. Whether you decide to take up one of our various offers or services or are a visitor to our site we assure you that we do not collect personal information from you unless you wish to provide it to us.

 **Information Collection and Use**  
There are two ways in which you can intentionally provide us with your personal information via our website, by entering competitions and by signing up to offers within our microsites. These use web forms to collect personal information in accordance with the offer or competition at hand. This will usually include your name, email address and postcode however on occasion it may also be necessary to ask for further demographic information such as your address and or telephone number or other information as required.

We collect this information in order to best communicate with you and to provide good service to our clients. By entering your details into a client microsite you will be joining their mailing list, this is used to communicate directly with you via our websites and to provide updates concerning both informational pieces and offers relevant to what you originally signed up to. Your details are held on a secure server and are separate to the main manchesterconfidential.com website. As such they will not be accessible to anyone other than **The Confidentials** staff. On occasion we may need to pass your details over to our clients in order to fulfil your requests and deliver on promised discounts or to deliver a prize. You will always be aware of this when submitting your information and under no circumstances will you be added to any third party email lists.

When you visit our website our computers will automatically record statistics about your visit. This information does not identify you personally, however we collect statistics such as how many people visit our website, users IP address, pages visited and links clicked in order to monitor the use of our website so that we can report back to clients and improve the way in which our website works.

 **Tell A Friend**  
If users of our website elect to use our referral service to inform friends about our site and services we may as for the friends name and email address. **The Confidentials** will store and use this information to send the friend an invitation. This information may also be used to provide information about our company and related products and services. The friend may contact us as detailed in the tell-a-friend message to request that no further communications be sent.

 **Opting out**  
Our belief is that all communications must be wholly consensual and should you elect to be removed from our mailing list or website you can at any time by visiting our unsubscribe page. A link to this page can be found at the bottom of any email communication you receive from us, alternatively you can log in to any of the confidential websites with your user name and password and opt-out from the user area found by clicking your name at the top of the site. We ask that you allow up to 48 hours for this to be fully processed by our system.

 **Security**  
The protection of all personal information we receive via our website visitors and subscribers is critical to our business. As such you should be assured that we have security measures in place to protect against the loss or misuse of any information we receive from you. As with any transmission over the internet there is always some risk involved. Thats why well never ask you for something we dont need and we will always treat your details as we do our own.

 **How can you update or correct your personal information**  
Should you need to update your personal information at any time you can email via our contact form with any new information, again we would ask that you allow us up to 24 hours to adjust your details on our system. Any further queries may be directed to [admin@theconfidentials.co.uk](mailto:admin@theconfidentials.co.uk).

 **Communications with Us**  
We have features within the site whereby our customers can submit information to us such as via contact forms. Where such submissions include requests for information, support or services we may forward them to our clients as needed to best respond to the specific request. We will keep a record of all such contacts for our internal administration purposes and to help us serve our subscribers better. Please note that letters to the editor and similar submissions may be made public.

 **Further Information**  
For further information on our privacy policy or for specific questions about how we use your data please contact [privacy@theconfidentials.co.uk](mailto:privacy@theconfidentials.co.uk)

 **Delivery policy**  
The majority of transactions on our websites relate to a service or experience rather than having a tangible product to deliver. In this instance a deposit is taken to secure a booking and a unique reference is provided digitally that allows the redemption of the offer. Where there are any promotions that include a tangible product the delivery details are outlined within the specific promotion. If you have any queries on this please contact [info@theconfidentials.co.uk](mailto:info@theconfidentials.co.uk)

 **Payment / Return / Refund / Cancellation Policy**

Membership payment policy

When you sign up for a Hero membership a recurring payment is set up. Funds will be debited from the card provided inline with your chosen payment cycle (monthly, quarterly or annually). Should you wish to cancel your recurring payment please contact [membership@theconfidentials.co.uk](mailto:membership@theconfidentials.co.uk).

Each partner with a promotion on Manchester Confidential outlines different policies; these are highlighted at the point of purchase. If there are any queries on these please address them to [info@theconfidentials.co.uk](mailto:info@theconfidentials.co.uk)

As a general rule a deposit is taken for restaurant bookings and we allow cancellations up to 48 hours prior to the reservation. If a refund is issued this will take 14 working days to process.

Membership can be cancelled by contacting [membership@theconfidentials.co.uk](mailto:membership@theconfidentials.co.uk). Cancellations need to be made prior to a recurring payment being debited. We do not offer refunds on any part of membership.

 **Contact information**  
If you have any queries on our policies please email [privacy@theconfidentials.co.uk](mailto:privacy@theconfidentials.co.uk)

 **Rant Facility - Terms of Use**

 **1\. Some General Rules**

  * We reserve the right to remove, at any time and without notice, any content from the Website whether it is content or comments. 
  * Refrain from using inappropriate language, including language that may look, sound like, stand for, hint at, abbreviate, or insinuate profanity, hate speech (including but not limited to racial, ethnic, or religious slurs), illegal drugs/controlled substances or illegal activities.
  * We reserve the right to contact your ISP regarding any inappropriate activities by you on the Service.
  * We reserve the right to immediately terminate or suspend anyone who fails to abide by these Terms of Use. The decision to suspend or terminate accounts will be made at the sole discretion of the site administrators. All account terminations (bannings) are final.

 **2\. Community Rules**   
The following conduct is not allowed on the Confidential Sites. The decision to moderate such conduct will be made at the sole discretion of the site moderators and administrators.

  *  **Illegal Activity:** Communications that violate or incite others to violate the law are not allowed.
  *  **Offensive Material:** Users may not transmit or encourage others to transmit material or links to content considered patently offensive in nature. This includes, but is not limited to, using vulgar, profane, or sexually explicit language in reference to race, religion, sexual orientation, culture, ethnicity, disability, nationality, or gender as a means of insult; violent material; using threatening, harassing, defamatory, hate-speech, or libellous language; and posting, requesting, linking to, or otherwise sharing material considered pornographic, obscene, graphic, or hate speech. Failing to abide by a warning that material or terms are offensive or prohibited is a violation.
  *  **Flooding, Invading, Disruptive Behaviour:** Behaviour that disrupts the website for other users, intentional or not, is prohibited. This includes, but is not limited to: Posting identical or near-identical messages or topics; or nonsensical messages in a single or multiple topics. Flooding an article with comments or any other similar behaviour is prohibited
  *  **Impersonation:** Impersonating other users by creating and/or using a user account with a name clearly intended to impersonate, mock, or antagonize another user, copying another user's profile information and/or signature, or otherwise falsely claiming to be another member is strictly prohibited.
  *  **Harassment/Stalking/Privacy:** Continual harassing behaviour directed towards a certain individual by another individual or group with the intent of creating an intimidating, offensive, or hostile environment on the website, with or without use of explicit or implicit threats, is strictly prohibited. Posting contact or other private information of any person (website user or not) is also prohibited.
